Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Showbox/Mediaplex Presents
A Showbox/Mediaplex Production
Executive Producer RYU Jeong-hun
SONG Kang-ho
GANG Dong-won
A long, long time ago,
there was a tree...
And a young man
who loved the tree.
Every single day
he came to the tree,
and collected
all falling leaves.
Hyung-sook,
l have to hang up.
- l'll call you back.
- Coming home...
this time for sure?
Of course,
no matter what.
You must teach her
to take daddy's call
even if she doesn't want to.
Maybe daddy didn't
educate her properly.
Educate?
lt's you, not me.
l gave her
the best education.
Sending her
to private school
isn't good education.
Sir! lt's Tae-soon!
You rarely saw her
- when you had the chance.
- Okay, fine.
l'll call you back later.
Don't bother.
l love you.
Bullshit!
Tae-soon, it's me.
Okay, l got it.
Thank you,
you're a good guy.
client
important work
guide
contact
second-cousin
Doesn't make sense.
How long will it take?
About 3 days.
3 day? Not good enough!
Move over.
What the...
Excuse me.
Which way is
to Johan Cathedral?
Johan Cathedral?
Stay on this street...
l could guide you better
if you give me a ride.
Been well?
My kid's first birthday
next month.
Are you happy?
Yeah, you?
l'm leaving soon.
You must miss them.
How about a u-turn?
No police around.
- Now?
- Now.
Hey,
where are you going?
l'm sorry sir
l think l lost them.
lncompetent bastard.
Keep driving and go home,
you idiot!
Everyone get ready
and standby.
We don't know
wherethey'll end up
so wait in the car.
Confirm last location.
- Go on.
- Yes, sir.
&nbsp
Shouldn't we call
the other team?
And give them
the credit?
We can take care
of it ourselves.
Excuse me.
l need to...
use the restroom.
Dance for me.
l said dance.
Trendy dance that
the kids here like.
Very nice.
Looks like
all our funding
went to dance classes.
Since you're more agile,
you come with me upstairs.
And you stay below.
What are you?
- Delivery man?
- Yeah.
Kyung-nam,
you look plain
even without the disguise.
You don't drive well,
get in the backseat.
lt's Gui Soong-min apartment!
Let's go!
Wait, who lives there?
Kim Sung-hak
Kim Jung-il's second cousin.
Fuck me.
Keep this.
After it's done, we'll part
on the first floor.
Rendezvous
at the terminal
and go back together.
Okay.
l can already feel
the bloodbath.
Accent in front,
out of the way!
lt's the director.
Lee Han-kyu here.
What do you think
you're doing?!
'Shadow' is on the move.
- lf we loose him...
- Shitbag!
Why didn't you
report this!
lt happened too quickly
so l'll report afterward
l got you.
That's all l need to do.
Who is it?
Morning,
l'm from the church.
ls Mr. Kim Sung-hak home?
He went to
the corner store.
You are... mother-in-law?
Yes, that's right.
Slow down, you'll trip.
l'm gonna get you!
What?
l don't think
this was necessary...
l'll be frank since
you're like my son.
Romantic Southerners
are whores.
Every one of them.
Look at them.
She married a defector
out of compassion and was killed
because of it.
Let's go in
We're here.
Where are you, Tae-soon?
You backstabbing rat,
take a good look.
You leached off our
nation's generosities
but publish a book
that taunt our leader?
l dreamt of killing you
every night.
- lt's apartment #1103.
- #1103...
You go first that way.
Clear the way!
- What's the floor?
- 11th floor!
- Comrade...
- Son of a bitch!
- He's just a child...
- Remember.
Our great nation
cannot have
a single fragile son.
How dare you
betray me?!
lt wasn't me.
l don't know anything.
Freeze!
l just live next door.
The boy was crying.
- Min-chul, head up.
- Yes, sir.
- No problem downstairs.
- Get up.
Hands up, asshole!
Target confirmed.
Check him.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
He's okay.
ls that you Min-chul?
Min-chul!
Son of a bitch!
What's going on?
Agent Ko!
Hey!
Get the car around
that side!
- Back off!
- Ko Kyung-nam!
- Agent Ko!
- Sir...
- Pull back right away!
- Sir, one went down!
Si-kyung!
Where's your mom?
- Take pictures of everything!
- Yes, sir.
Ko, give me the physical
description!
What's going on?
Over there, more people
coming out of there.
Yes, sir!
l said pull back!
Seal that exit!
Yes, sir. Out of the way!
6' tall wearing black suit
Out of the way!
- What the hell!
- Get in!
Are you okay?
- l'm fine, get in!
- Hurry.
- What about agent Kim?
- He's dead.
Shit!
Watch out!
Move! Move!
Step on the brake!
Shit!
Are you okay?
Go! Keep driving!
Yes, sir!
Watch out for the people!
Move! Out of the way!
Be careful.
l got you now.
- Floor it!
- Goddammit!
What the hell?
Why didn't you
request backup?!
Why?!
We can't keep up
with their pace through
normal chain of commands.
We must act first...
You be ready.
Hello?
l'm the agent in charge.
We're not
after you or Tae-soon.
Our target is
a North Korean assassin,
a high ranking officer.
He goes by many names
but commonly known
as Shadow.
That's who we want.
With your help,
we can get him.
l promise you
we'll help both of you
if we get him.
Tae-soon said
you graduated
from Kim Jung-il's
military school.
Aside from that,l don't know
anything about you.
Not even your face.
We can talk later
if you're in a situation.
l'll give you my number
Memorize it
011 865 92...
Betrayal, unforgivable
Two leaders
got together...
for the first time
in 55 years.
Hold on.
l suffered through
salary reduction
and disciplinary actions.
Now you want my throat?
Getting honorable
discharge
before official
staff reduction
is a generous way for us
to thank you for the work.
Having too many agents
on the field
is too much burden
for the agency.
Burden?
Were we getting paid
to fool around?
Our job is to catch
spies so
our people can
sleep soundly.
Times are changing.
Hostility is not
the answer anymore.
Their field operations are
coming to a halt.
Fine. But at least
let us finish this
before cutting us off.
l won't leave before
catching Shadow first.
Agent Lee
Stay out of this.
You've caused more
than enough problems.
l lost my teammates
who were like my family.
But l still have to
feed my real family.
You're divorced.
But l'm still
paying alimony.
What am l saying?
l can't just step down
during my prime.
This is why you
don't get anywhere.
You don't catch spies
to make money.
You're the reason
why our agency is
getting the bad rep.
Looks like this was decided
even before this meeting.
ls it because
of field problems?
Or getting divorced?
Just stick to one reason
for termination.
What did you say?
Do you know why l didn't
bother reporting?
What's the point?
You're goddamn
pushover and a tool.
You bastard!
Once is plenty enough.
Where do you think you are?!
Calm down, Agent Lee.
Let go of me!
Changing times? Fuck that!
l'm a federal agent
who catch commies!
6 years later
Hey, don't do it!
- You wanted it.
- lt won't be good.
- You were gonna do it.
- lt's dirty.
Hey miss
your food's great.
Could l take some photos
and post it online?
Online where?
An online club
for finding good restaurants.
Sure.
Come here
and give me a hand.
Quickly, customers
are waiting.
Here it is.
There're address, phone number
and even directions.
For extra $2,000,
we can bring her
back for you.
No, l'll go myself.
Okay.
Thank you.
Looks like your life
is hard enough.
l hope that
you'll be happier
when your wife comes back.
l'll be on my way then.
Hey, Yoon-ji.
Daddy?
l'm working right now.
Don't just like mommy.
You have to be good.
Yoon-ji,
don't call me too much.
Mommy won't like it.
Mommy's not there?
Don't worry about me, okay?
Hello?
Hey! lt's slanted!
Quit fooling around!
l'm paying each
of you $1,500.
You guys
are highway robbers!
Specialists in finding
runaway foreign wives
Chief!
Congratulations
on your promotion!
You didn't need to
come on a rainy day.
These guys were brokering
international marriages.
Vietnamese,
Filipino, Cambodian and
other Asian countries.
They bring the girls over,
marry them
then convince them
that there're better men.
They're ripping off
poor farmers.
Look at this appalling face.
This is the boss.
He's half Korean
but worse than the Vietnamese.
But this is
an organization.
l know you're the best
man for this.
They must be stirring
quite a bit.
The department put high
reward on them.
About $60,000.
Sixty?
l hear they go to
the factory
where many
Vietnamese work.
The boss goes
nuts over soccer.
Go over there.
Sweep thoroughly
Playing basketball
in a soccer field, morons!
Hey!
What are you doing?
- You're not here to watch soccer!
- Okay.
- Jae-hwan.
- Yes, sir.
Do you see that guy
in Yankees hat?
Fat guy in white suit.
Yes.
l can't verify
from my position,
but what do you think?
l'll check up close.
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Not yet!
That crazy idiot!
l think it's him.
Should l grab him?
Do you want to get killed?
Get out of there!
Okay.
Jae-hwan! Jae-hwan!
Sang-chul,
l can't spot Jae-hwan.
Jae-hwan?
Did you see a guy
in Yankees hat?
A what? Yangi?
Find Jae-hwan first,
quick!
Why aren't you
answering me!
What are you doing here?
Boss is looking for you.
And why's your
radio set off?
You can't...
Boss, we're
fucked here.
All right, l'll be there.
Hey!
Do your worst, come at me.
That's it.
l'll get
the minions,
grab that bastard
over there.
Got it? Now!
Hey, where are you going?!
Shit!
Fake? Fake?
lt's a gas gun!
Hey, hey, stop, stop!
Stop it!
l called the cops.
Stop!
l'm letting you live
because the game was tied.
l'll kill you...
if we meet again.
Shut it down!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Are you a worker here?
You're a Korean.
Are you a cop?
No, l run a small...
They're wanted men.
l was after
the reward money...
with a gas gun.
Your name is?
What for?
Just want to thank you.
Ki-joon!
Go treat your wounds.
Hey!
What is it?
lt's weird to ask you
this like this,
but would you consider
working for me?
What type of work?
Finding people.
lt's a real enterprise
and well commended.
Looked like finding wasn't
the only thing.
Ah, that happens once every
10 years if l'm lucky.
l was helping
out local cops.
l'm find where l am.
Of course.
But l noticed that
you may be
an asset to me.
Your name was...?
Park Ki-joon.
Your fighting skills...
l mean, physical condition...
and you speak
Vietnamese well.
Where did you
learn to speak?
Most of our workers are
Vietnamese, so...
lt's perfect.
l'm in the business of
finding
Vietnamese women.
We haven't known each
other long
but why don't you
come work for me?
l like
my current work.
Of course.
lt's time
for me to go.
How about you call me.
Park Ki-joon
my ass.
l got you Ji-won.
Boss, are you okay?
Key.
Here.
Live well,
stop wasting your life.
He's really leaving.
Boss!
- Hello?
- lt's me.
- Who?
- lt's your daddy, idiot!
Who? Agent Lee?
- Kyung-nam.
- Yes, sir!
- l just hit the jackpot.
- Huh?
Who is it?
Pork feet!
Pork?
Sir!
You still go
around like this?
ls that true?
Like l said.
He's there as the manager.
Ji-won didn't
recognize your face?
Of course not,
he has never seen me.
But you recognized him?
l knew right away.
Man, weren't you surprised?
Did he not clue in?
l pretended
to be oblivious.
lf l acted like
l knew him,
it would've been
game over.
You know l have a knack
for acting.
ln any case, thank you.
My arrest rate
isn't great lately.
- Kyung-nam.
- Yeah?
l didn't call you
to hand him over.
Aren't you going to
report him in?
l'm leading this.
You're just
supporting me.
Do you get it?
No, l don't.
Keep it away from
the agency, you idiot!
Okay...
What's the reward
for spies nowadays?
$100,000
And spy ring?
Huh?
Unification Policy
Research Facility
You don't look well.
l met an NlS agent
a few days ago by chance.
Lee Han-kyu,
who looked for Tae-soon
and me 6 years ago.
Lee Han-kyu?
Yes. He asked me to work for him
as if he didn't recognize me.
Looks like
a private agency.
On the surface.
l'm sure
it's just his cover.
- So?
- l don't know.
Maybe submit
an undercover report.
Ji-won.
How about
- surrendering?
- You made me
into what l am
in military school.
And now you're asking me
to betray my country?
Like you?
Watch your mouth!
So what are you
going to do?
l've been on the
run for 6 years.
lt's time
to end this.
l won't visit you
again.
Won't it be better
to switch him over?.
ln an unofficial
route.
Like Tae-soon?
The spies are nuts
over working
for us after their
funding ran dry.
l already asked him
to work with me.
Yeah?
What did he say?
But he likes his work.
- What...
- Anyway,
Come relief me when you're done.
- Hello?
- Sir, it's me.
Why didn't you show up
yesterday?
- The director's here.
- Hey!
- l'll call you back.
- You're the one who called.
ls he gone?
lt's Park Ki-joon,
we met a couple of days ago.
Who? Park Ki-joon?
Ah, Mr. Park!
Park Ki-joon!
Yes, sure.
How can l help you?
Ah, l see.
- Had lunch yet?
- Not yet.
How about a burger?
l don't like burgers.
Anyway, you chose wisely.
We have to push our
strongest traits.
Even the office workers
look for a way
out in their 40s.
l haven't
decided yet.
l wanted to hear
the conditions.
l see. You must need
a lot of money.
Downpayment
for an apartment.
Apartment? How big?
About 100m©÷
A self-made man,
so young too.
Apartment...
That's our
nation's problem.
People become rich over it,
families get broken up,
but it also unites
others, like us.
How much will you pay me?
l paid my old employees
$2,000 total...
But l can't give you that,
it's hardly enough for you.
$2,500?
Add another 200?
$3,000! Housing included!
l'm sorry...
l get that
with my current job.
Of course,
but l'm not done yet.
There's also incentives.
How much will that be?
Usually incentives
are...10%.
30%...No higher.
When do l start?
Right now.
You don't need to
bring gifts every time.
Bro, it's Thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving is in 4 months.
Who's he?
Ki-joon, greet him.
He's my new employee.
Yeah?
Where are you from?
Why are yo u asking
stuff like that?
lt's Haenam, sir.
Really? Where in Haenam?
Why? Don't l look country?
lt's not that,
you don't have a dialect.
Don't you know
each other?
No, it's not that.
Bro,
l have something to ask.
Take a look.
Boss, why
are you following me?
Right, right.
Hey, please stop.
You won't go far like this.
You're gonna
tire yourself out.
No! No!
One case completed.
ls that absolutely
necessary?
- What?
- The cuffs.
Ma'am, l'm sorry.
l'll uncuff you at home.
Please uncuff her,
this is torture.
lf she escapes
after we get her,
she's gone for good.
How can she escape
while the car's running?
Listen, Ki-joon.
Do you have to
make it unpleasant
on our first day
together?
Did l beat her?
Or curse at her?
ls that any better
than either?
Listen to me. l have pride
in my work just like you do.
Why? l keep this nation's
families together.
We're not cops and
they haven't committed
any crimes.
Please treat them
like humans.
Ki-joon. There's a
dark side to our work.
What we do will have
positive effects...
Bastard,
an adult is talking.
You could do that
while we're moving!
Shit!
Come on in.
You can stay here with me.
lt's my office but
comfortable enough to stay.
Make yourself at home.
Side effect of living alone.
l'll use
the upstairs and
you can use
this space here.
Please don't come up.
lt just fell.
lt's a kitchen knife!
l must be nuts.
All this for money.
lnfiltrated as an employee,
lnternational Task Force
Tracing Son Tae-soon's
whereabouts
Address - Seoul,
Mapo-gu...
Still not back?
l haven't slept a wink.
What if he figures it out
and brings Shadow?
How could he know me?
Cut the crap,
l'm hanging up.
Where have you been?
Come in.
You have a guest too.
Where is that commie!
Where are the cuffs?
Yesterday, Ji-won...
Where were you?
This?
l was just testing it.
Doesn't work well.
Ki-joon,
the key please.
Just throw it.
What do we do today?
Yes, Mr. Jo.
We'll call you
when we find her.
Haven't slept well?
Should l drive?
No, only l drive this car.
That could've been nasty.
We're here.
You start from this side.
And l'll cover this area.
Rather than
an aimless approach,
you go diagonally like this.
And l take the opposite route.
lf not we flip
45 degrees and try again.
We'll get her for sure.
l know that method.
Where did you learn it?
Online.
lt's an old trick.
All right,
let's give it a try.
Yeah.
Any progress yet?
Progress?
l might be paying him $3,000.
$3,000?!
That's just base pay.
l had to lure him
with 30% incentive too...
What kind of communist
is so fixated on money?
Where is he spending
the money?
Says it's for
an apartment, shit.
All the while his boss is renting.
He pretends to be noble and
tells me l'm being inhumane.
He doesn't answer
anything properly.
He's practically
the boss around here!
l gotta find a way soon.
His salary's going
to be bigger than...
Find her?
Goddamn commie.
That's why
l have to find my wife.
Have you seen her?
We don't know.
Come on, play!
Me? lt's my turn?
This granny's hand
is worthless.
You could put your
hand down and call it.
No mercy when
it comes to gambling.
l found her.
Who's the other one?
They were together.
They must've escaped
with each other.
How did you bring them?
l convinced them...
Humanely.
l got the humane part,
but how did you
find them so fast?
ls that a problem?
No.
How old are you?
6 years old.
6?
l don't know
how to thank you...
Normally $2,000 for finding,
bringing back $2,000
for a total of $4,000
She wanted to come on
her own, so it's okay.
But if it wasn't for us...
l must repay you, humanely.
Of course, humanely.
Very humane, indeed.
What the hell?!
Get it! Quickly!
l got it, got it!
Nice! Nice!
Cuff it if we're
bringing it home.
Jesus Christ!
Move that somewhere!
lt's just food.
Let's not start already.
l don't want it, you eat it.
Delicious.
Genuine chicken broth.
Been a while since
someone cooked for me.
What happened
to your wife and daughter?
l wasn't much
of a husband to her.
This work can be demanding.
She remarried a British man
and moved to
England.
His name is Albert and
renamed my daughter Amy.
What kind of stupid name
is Amy?
Don't you want to see her?
l haven't seen her
once after they left.
l want to buy her a home
when she gets married.
You will be able to.
Of course, that's what l'll do.
Be good to your wife
when you get married.
NlS agent Lee Han-kyu
Divorced and lives alone.
Chicken broth
Okay! One more day!
Are you going out?
Go out and meet
some people too.
You're too young
to be cooked up in here.
Meet who?
A friend or a girlfriend?
No friends in Seoul.
And not interested
in girls.
Then go have fun
somewhere.
Don't waste your vacation
like this.
l'll just watch some TV.
Hello?
Hi, Yoon-ji.
Daddy's working.
What are you doing?
ls that so?
Albert's teaching you piano?
Must've been nice...
Do you like your new dad?
Like me better?
Birthday present?
Digital camera?
You can buy that there.
l'll send money so
ask your mom for it.
Daddy has to go, honey.
Could you cook something
nice for me? -Boss
Tae-soon! Over here!
Thank you, as always.
Let's all live well.
Quite cozy.
You sold your country
and comrades so you can
live like this?!
l'm treated like a traitor and
l can't go back
because of you!
You did this to me!
Say something!
l want to live.
l want to live!
Shit...
l'm sorry.
What about the family?
Went to the in-laws
for a few days.
How did you know
l was here?
Didn't you meet
an NlS agent earlier?
No!
l'm not part
of that anymore.
And Lee is
not an agent anymore.
What are you talking about?
He took responsibilities
for that
botched operation
and was fired.
He doesn't work
for them anymore.
The director was asking
about you.
Me? What for?
ls hell freezing over?
He's up there for a long time.
lt was hard getting it.
lt's not even released yet.
lt's no biggie
triangulating a cell,
don't make a fuss over
a GPS tracker.
This will work
even when cells don't.
l'll take it back
if you don't like it.
Forget that.
Give me the receiver.
No one knows, right?
Yeah, okay.
There's a new development.
A big news?
l think something's up
in the North.
Yeah?
What's going on?
Go watch the news.
7th undercover report
You're back?
TV all day? Always
the same music show.
You trying to be a singer?
There is a breaking news.
North Korea will
carry out
a nuclear missile test
within a few days.
For our proud nation,
we have developed
nuclear weapon.
Why are those fuckers
acting up again?
lt's been known
that North Korea was
developing nuclear arsenal.
But this is the first official proof
of its existence.
This development
will renew
the tension
between two nations.
They claim that
the weapons will not be used
unless provoked
by the US...
What the hell!
What's with the suit?
Going somewhere nice?
Looks great.
There's a soiree.
A soiree?
lt's reunion.
l wanted to meet
some old friends.
What kind of school?
Primary.
Ah, elementary school.
Really old friends then.
Go on.
l might be late.
Have fun and
don't drink too much.
Kyung-nam!
- lt's time!
- Sir?.
He's going to
a school reunion.
So?
Think, you moron!
How could a guy
from the North go to
a South reunion?
Shadow?
Kyung-nam!
l'll send photos
of his associates
and plate numbers
so cross reference.
Keep driving!
Go, go!
l got a report that
he passed out at a bar.
l put a tail on him.
He doesn't normally drink.
Something's up.
Professor, producer, pastor
A commie producer,
no wonder this country's
going to shit.
Hello, l have some
special scoop,
could l talk to
producer Min Kyu-chul?
He went to China
on an assignment for a month.
Ah, on an assignment.
- l see.
- What's the scoop?
l shoved it up your asshole.
Professor and the producer
left yesterday
and only the pastor's
still in the country.
Why didn't you tell me earlier!
Have they realized
What we're up to?
A pastor.
l got you red bastards.
- Head for Hwagok.
- Yes, sir.
Pastor Lee?
Please come in.
Thank you.
You're all finished,
rat fuckers!
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
We're Song Ji-won's friends.
l live with him.
Live together?
Don't know Song Ji-won?
How about Park Ki-joon.
Ah, ln-joon!
Are you referring
to Jo ln-joon?
ln-joon is our client.
Ow, my arm...
ln-joon
has family
in the North.
Wife and a daughter,
but he hasn't seen them
in 7 years, l'm told.
ln-joon was betrayed and
abandoned by
his own country.
He can't surrender
because of family
back home even
if he wanted to.
He couldn't wait
any longer so
he wanted to bring
his family,
so he came to us.
But
it was more costly
than he thought,
and l didn't hear
from him for a while.
This past summer
he came back, saying
he can get the money.
Apartment payment.
Then?
But before
we could get them out,
the nuclear incident happened.
So naturally the border
tightened up
Producer Min and Prof. Hwang
took off yesterday.
l guess this might be
the last chance.
Are you going to
report Ji-won now?
Wait a couple of day.
He's bringing
his family back.
Won't he surrender then?
Pretty, huh?
l went to Vietnam
and met 120 girls
in an hour
and she was the most
beautiful one.
lf a man's
going to remarry,
he must choose
the beautiful one.
Are you married?
No.
Young people
these days think it's better
- to live alone but...
- What's your wife's name?
Eunwenddi Ddooi An
Or Won Soo-young in Korean.
Beautiful but too smart.
Making a fuss over
some beatings.
- You could just go there.
- Thank you.
He'll beat her
if she comes back, right?
Hey, mind you
own business.
His family is not
your concern.
Capitalism is about
finding happiness
by taking another's wealth.
That's not a crime, okay?
Do you find happiness in
looking for
other men's women?
Watch your mouth!
You don't know
anything about me.
lsn't that the same?
Quit if you don't like it.
Bitch and moan.
Ddooi An? Miss Ddooi An?
Mr. Jung asked us
to find you.
Please come with us.
l'm not a Vietnamese,
l'm half Korean!
We already know.
Who are you?
Aren't you all illegal?
Should l get the
immigration down here?
Move!
Out of the way!
- l said l'm a Korean!
- Do something!
¢Ü l love this country!
Tihong! Call Tihong!
Sure, you're a Korean,
l have no doubt.
l'm sure about that.
Please stop!
Do you see them
only as money?
Son of a bitch!
Don't pretend to be humane.
You need the money too!
Remember the apartment?
No wonder your family left you.
What?
What did you just say?
You really want to
start this?
You bastard!
What are you waiting for!
Get out!
Did you see the news?
Our team lost.
You're all dead.
l didn't see the match.
Once in 10 years or so, huh?
lt's because we didn't
settle last time.
What do you think?
You?
Can you manage?
Damn it.
Go, you bastard!
l said go!
Are you okay?
l'm not okay.
Look at that traffic.
An accident?
Ah, it's Thanksgiving.
Everyone's heading home.
But look at us.
Bruised and battered.
You're lucky to be spending
Thanksgiving with family.
Did your husband
beat you a lot?
l can have
Korean citizenship
2 years after wedding.
But he won't
sponsor me for it.
Saying l'd leave him
when l get it.
Whenever l ask him
about it
he hits me.
l have a favor.
Could l see my sister on the way?
She also married here.
l haven't seen her
in over 5 years.
l beg of you.
Newan!
Sister, is this really you?
Ki-joon!
Yeah?
Let's just go.
Too bad about the payment.
Eh, it's only
a couple of bucks.
Why did you let that boss go?
When we get the reward,
you're gonna leave.
l'd hate to let you go once
you have your apartment.
You'll make me
more money over time.
Cheers!
While Thanksgiving took
all over the country,
North Korea has...
Thanksgiving is no big deal.
UN Security Council announced that
they will enforce sanctions
when North Korea proceeds
the nuclear tests.
Therefore, the Government
convenes a meeting
to seek a solution with advisors.
Especially Prof. Ji,
Unification Policy Researcher would
advise on expected venues
for the nuclear test.
How long have
we worked together?
About 4 months.
That long already?
Don't you miss
your family?
l'm divorced!
What's the point
in missing them?
Family is family
when we're together.
Ki-joon,
could you call me brother?
Forget it,
why are you my brother?
Come on, just once.
Let's just pretend.
No.
Cocky prick.
Fine, l don't like you either
You up?
What are you doing?
Fortunately
the store was open.
lt's late but you should
put on a service
for your parents.
Why? Don't know
how to do it?
What's your mother's
maiden name?
Kim, An-dong district.
An-dong Kim?
l'll give it a try.
l hear the North have
services nowadays.
Sit...
Would l report you
during a service?
Did you know who l am?
Did you know all along?!
Answer me!
Stop this, Ki-joon.
No, you're Ji-won,
Song Ji-won.
Why did you keep me around?
Why didn't you report me?
You're a small fish.
A spy ring would be
a different story.
l found out that
you were abandoned
by your organization.
So, now you want to sell me off.
How much will they pay you?
Lower the knife.
Who knows what'll happen.
lf everything goes well,
we could just
continue our business.
What will we do with our skills?
We could make it big
if we cooperate.
Then we hike up
the fees and
make some serious dough.
And we'll help people too.
Go on,
l'll give your parents a bow too.
Go on.
Hello? Oh, Kyung-nam.
What? Son-tae?
Where are you?
Yeah... yeah, okay.
l have to go out.
Something happened
to a friend.
Looks like the job of Shadow.
lt must be him.
ls he back?
l want to live.
l want to live!
lt's Song Ji-won!
Ji-won, do you remember me?
We met briefly 6 years ago.
Lee told me all about you.
l know about your situation.
Shadow is active again.
We just want to find him.
We can protect your secrecy.
Do you see me...
as a spineless traitor?
Catch him!
Don't let him get away!
Catch up to him!
Kyung-nam, let him go!
Sir, what are you saying?!
You know
Shadow has abandoned him.
He has nothing to do with this.
But he may still
be a link to Shadow.
Please, give him 2 days.
When his family comes over,
he'll surrender.
How could we catch spies
with mercy and compassion?
You're putting me
in an awkward position.
Hey, Lee Han-kyu!
Please stop the car.
Hand over the GPS,
and tell me about Ji-won.
We'll pay you handsomely.
Still same as always.
What are you going
to do with him?
He's blacklisted by Shadow.
Would he still contact him?
So incompetent...
l'm asking for the GPS so that
you don't get involved in this.
l could have you thrown in jail
if you don't comply.
Times have changed,
you can't just threaten
a civilian. Money?
Perhaps a million?
Stop crediting yourself
for others' work.
- Nothing's changed around here!
- Hey! Hey!
Get back in here!
There's no room
for mistake.
Shoot to kill if you have to.
Ji-won, pick up the phone!
There's a GPS tracker
in your watch.
They know where you are.
So throw out your watch.
What's his position?
He's at the bus terminal.
He's on his cell phone.
Producer Min, it's ln-joon.
Yes, ln-joon.
l called you because this
may be the last time.
what are you saying?
l may have caused harm
to my family.
So please continue
the work even without me.
l'm hanging up now.
We're exposed.
Take out the exposed
agents and
track him until he makes
contact with Shadow.
Current position, Jongro.
Jongro? Who's there?
Our country is giving you
a last chance.
Prove yourself.
l can already feel
the bloodbath.
Contact the local
district authorities!
What's going on?
l don't know,
we just received an order.
lt's probably nothing.
He has a gun! Block him!
Coming to you,
He's within 40m.
- Spread out!
- Yes, sir.
What are you waiting for?
Finish the job.
Ji-won! Song Ji-won!
What happened?
What about Shadow?
Anyway, l'm glad you're okay.
There's no time,
give me your watch.
GPS tracker is in here.
Why didn't you answer
the phone?
NlS knows your position,
they'll swarm the area soon.
They might kill you,
so get out of here.
Professor, are you all right?
Get out of here.
What's wrong?
Did the party send you?
Who sent you?
What is he saying?
Fucking traitor.
Talks too goddamn much.
lt wasn't
an order from above?
What?
Mind your own business.
Did you kill Tae-soon
on your own?
Killing traitors
is a privileged job
for our nation.
You're one of them now.
l'm not a traitor.
Didn't you try
to defect your family?
What happened to my family?
What do you think?
What happened to them?!
Ji-won, you dumb idiot.
l lost my colleagues, job
and my family because of you.
lf you don't drop
the gun, he'll die.
Go ahead.
Kill me!
Stop it, Ji-won.
Bastard!
Over here!
- Call the HQ!
- Okay.
- Jin-woo, go down.
We go down together.
Ji-won!
No, Shadow is still alive!
- What about Ji-won?
- We couldn't verify.
- He's still alive!
- Ji-won!
Still alive!
Romantic bastards...
He's dead.
Cancel backup
and call paramedics.
Are you okay?
Ji-won, wake up!
l...
didn't... betray anyone...
l know.
Wake up!
Ji-won!
Hurry up!
Call me when you're cut off.
Brother!
l've recovered well
and doing all right.
lsn't it Yoon-ji's
birthday soon?
Go see her for a change.
Don't just stay home
and wonder.
Perhaps it's time for me
to leave for somewhere familiar.
l don't think
l belong here either.
lt seems too hard
to buy a house and
raise Hyo-sun here.
lf there's any chance,
we shall meet again.
This is called PMP.
Pictures, movies
and even internet.
My daughter begged me for it.
l'm sure
your daughter will love it.
Anyway, take care
of things while l'm away.
Yes boss, have a good flight!
This is lnternational Task Force.
Miss...
Yes, sir.
ls it open bar
in business class?
That's right
l could bring you
one if you like.
Then can you get me
the most expensive
whiskey on the rocks?
l'll prepare it right away.
Only village idiot
drinks whiskey
before the take off.
How could someone
who only eats burgers know
the difference between
good and shit?
Right?
SECRET REUNlON
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org